Voices collide, the storm and the flame
Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive
In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive
Who's awake? We're awake
Who's afraid? Let it break
From shadows to starlight, the truth will be shown
The Psyche awakens, you're never alone
Expect the unexpected.
It's psyche's show terrible trolls in the dark take their stand the angels are dancing torchlight in hand
Let's start the show
Hey, oh
I'm not feeling good today, but then it's like I thought everything else is going on
No big deal, I'm not drinking tonight, I've been sleeping all day, I'm ready to sleep more,
I like to sleep sometimes when I'm like that. Um, I just thought I'd say hi.
Um, this channel is going pretty good, it seems like I want to have like 500 subscribers on it,
Okay, cool here and say hi. I've been dreaming all day
dream in
baby
It's right on top of the keyboard right on top of the keyboard and stream
No, no, bg west ways. You're lame bg. Why don't I just like end you from the stream?
It's like a better idea
So lame so lame little like yes, man
Why don't you go lick beat his butthole and leave me alone? Okay?
Not in the mood. You probably tell that and then you'll write it on me. I'm gonna end you in the stream. Okay
Your little weasel
My rest of my friends, hi friends, thank you for being here
Oh, yeah, I am out with you for a little bit.
Here, did I put my link up?
I'll put my link up.
If anyone wants to come and say hi.
Just like, just having really weird, crime-filled kind
of dreams, like where one of them
I remember there is like some kind of like.
Dang like there's something there's something like them. There's some kind of missing like I don't know
Contraband or something and it's like and then it's like we open like this thing from the freezer
It was like this fish and it was in this dead fish in the freezer and
Then the people got it
I think was the criminals that found it and they're like and we're gonna let's look at sign up with a fish to find fish
You know you have worms and then they pull out all these worms and they put them all over us
And so it's kind of scary and the second one I was like
Trying to find my way around this hotel or like this hotel and it was like we're looking for somebody and there's this lady there
And it was like and everything was like so old-fashioned that we are all the movie all the restaurants really 1920s
Yeah, I don't like to I like to hide people but it's like you know, it's coming in a rude way, you know
and say hi, I don't know, because he's just a rude person, so they're so rude people.
Especially when people are going through things, like you don't even know how bad
things are that they're going through. I mean sometimes I think, oh, you know, even like just
losing my channel is like the icing on like the shit cake that makes serve sometimes, but...
You're gonna like really like think that's when you want to attack people by attacking when they're like, you know
We're in a different time. Yeah, it was a different timeline, but it was like
It wasn't like I was like dressed like a you know, like a 1920s gangsters and flappers or it was like it was like
Kind of like there was old old restaurants
And it was a different timeline because yeah, I was younger
And a lot of the dreams my dad was alive. Did I eat? No, not today. I had a cookie. I had a cookie. That was good
So unfortunately
But um
I'm kind of like a mess right now
But I do have to I do and I'm out of weed too, but I do have this tobacco I can smoke from our lawn for real quick
Yeah, I shouldn't have probably come on, but I just wanted to come home for a little bit. Say hi
Um, I think it's, I think it's, um, I think I missed my, I missed my, uh, my, my thing
because I think probably McDonald's was open, but so sweet, so sweet, but, um, I do have
like, um, McDonald's, like some like biscuit, I have biscuits, okay?
So they're not just biscuits. They're biscuit sandwiches. Oh, sweetie. Thank you so much
Probably is a little I think it's like probably oh actually
For you 1144 what's up, I don't know
I love you. Hey, hey, how are you doing Rudy? You know Rudy is you're my little sleeping buddy today
Whenever I woke up Rudy was right on top of me
Cuddled up sleeping
Hey, Jamie, how are you today or tonight? It's just such a weird day. It was like it's kept sleeping
I was like, oh, I don't want to be awake right now.
Thank you.
Maybe I'll show you a video I made last night, then.
Oh.
I'll hang out for a while here.
and crossed the line. She was Satan's ex with that fiery stare. Told me my rising sign like
she actually cared. I cracked a joke, baby oil slipped inside. She blocked my name, now I'm dead inside.
feels exposed you were my queen my tarot flame now i just cry while i play your name on a loop
like a cursed old spell amma without you i'm stuck in hell
i was fake elan i was nick cage too
And she's getting old, Emma, if you can hear me, I'm still in the algorithm, I still refresh
your channel, just to see your face in 1080p, we could have been Saratak royalty, but now,
now I'm just a ghost in the live stream for you.
Just whisper my name
Who's like smoke on a horizon?
No one can touch flame
Eyes, lips, the twist lies into truth
Every glance of
Presses like a cat on shattered glass each step of spillage
Whisper a gamble, your pulse effuses your trust again
Voice of the dawn, where the climb's begun
Words like pillars, fire in my hands
I build a temple, long shifting sands
Capricorn rising, storm in my eyes
Aquarius moonlight, thunder cracks the skies
Banner of love, secrets I keep
Secrets are key
Visions made flesh, I declare it now.
Autumn leaves and the gavel fall.
Through death and dawn, I will guide them all.
Rebel stars in the tribal flame.
Dreams cross borders, none stay the same.
at the edge of the sea, a scar.
It was a spark, not a throne
All I ever needed was a light to call my own
All I ever dreamed was someone new here
The voice in the dark say, you belong here
All I ever wanted was truth in the static
A little bit of real in the world, so dramatic
Can't my calm while the crowd threw stones
It was a mirror that saw me not the myth or the mass they all keep drawing the carnivals coming
But this time it's bright filled with misfits who learn to love the night
See I've been chained by my own reflection, but I burn those ropes divine insurrection now
I move clean through chaos and chatter gold from the madness. That's how come this matter
your name to bless your gift they laughed when i fell but i danced in the dirt every scar i got
just rewrote my worth all i ever wanted was to free my fear to turn my pain into something
Thank you so much for patient.
Hey, what's up?
Hey, this is pretty cool.
I like this one.
I know at BlackRG, sometimes when people have private phone
calls and stuff happening, and you know what?
This isn't monetized.
And you're not doing me any favors right now.
So why do boys matter to you?
Come on.
I didn't want to come on tonight, but I was like, you know what?
I do it because I love you guys.
I do.
Yeah, I'm not mad at you. I'm not thank you for being here. I appreciate everyone and everyone came to my channel like this new one and stuff
I mean it was already already built, you know, and I appreciate you guys so much. It's like because I
could feel like in a really bad situation right now or like nobody nobody was watching anymore or I
Don't know or just like laughing at me and stuff. I got a lot of support
I didn't I never even heard the laughter about it. No other than that one jerk that tried to do it and stuff. I
I like to blame myself for it. I like to blame myself for it, though.
Like, that's not a porn bomb myself.
I'm a porn myself, because someone told me I was looking at Martina Big,
who's like this woman with a huge breast and like, you know,
she, she, she colored her skin black and like, I was searching for it.
All this porn came up and then I was like, and I share my screen, show something.
And it was all this porn and it wasn't me watching it. It was.
It's not even my like really type. Anyway, I did it. I did it.
Okay. Anyway. Oh, cool. Anyone want to come up and chat? Come on up guys. I put the link.
Every midnight I get to work on my on my site some more. I want to show you how it's going so far
It's like going really good, but not a hundred percent
I'll show you how it looks so far, and then we'll see how it how it picks it up
It is cult k u l t o f p s y c h e dot com. Okay, and you can see how it looks. Okay, so I'm gonna share my screen
And I've got the memberships working through this site now.
Share my screen.
Why is it all blurry?
Make sure to screen.
Oh, window.
There we go.
Yo.
Well, here's my website.
I mean, that's how it looks so far, just CC.
It looks pretty good.
So, hey, Canada, I welcome back to my show
and thank you for...
Coming to the new channel, I don't know if you noticed I'm on a new channel. I did
Okay, good. Well, I appreciate you coming here. How are you tonight? Not bad, buddy? Sorry the other one got shut down
Hey, you know what happens and it's like, you know, it's better. It happens now than a few years from now or something like that
What was the reason for it? You know
There is some kind of porn somewhere
That they the AI picked up and it was like instead of just giving a warning or saying or deleting the episode
They just said we're deleting the channel. They said you can appeal
They gave me 600 letters to appeal like 600 like characters to use and I put it all in 600 characters and best I could
30 minutes later I got our things as well we're not we don't see the in the first
evil future adding this channel back and so I just went over to this one and uh but you know
it's just unfortunate I was under a heavy attack by people too like I'm just constantly I'm anti
flagging campaigns and um privacy thing privacy strikes and I mean all this stuff I was just
barely hanging on by a thread but I didn't have any strikes at the time so kind of unfortunately
That shit's crazy
Yeah, everyone has to realize it's like unless you're Logan Paul
And making them like hundreds of thousands of dollars are probably not gonna care too much about
They're gonna care more about the advertiser's gonna care more about the you know everything else
And so I'm just a little tiny little little an important
fish and fish in the sea and in YouTube world, but
Anyway, I'm actually I'm actually I'm kind of like it's I mean I'm looking at the positives of it where I did get to like you know
There's probably a lot of those old videos that I probably don't want up there like yeah
I don't know the price of embarrassing moments that I'm probably glad are gone forever that I didn't know how to take out and
Well, if there's a silver lining, then that's all right.
Yeah, there's always, there's always, and it's like, what?
And especially when you can't do something about it,
if I mean, if I could like, if there's a possibility of like,
I mean, maybe down the line, they'll say.
Oh, you know, you can go join the pilot program and like read because the people that talked about Co vid and stuff like that and their channels taken down, they're all getting them back right now.
Like, um, and so they've kind of changed.
You know, it's changed the things change over time. Hopefully maybe pornography will be less of a big deal and future thing.
Yeah, hopefully we can all just get naked and fuck on cam.
Yeah, I'd like to do that. Are you down?
Not today.
Not today. Maybe some day.
Yeah.
I have 24 people in here.
My last few months, I've had
basically, oh look at that. Nice avatar.
Cute guy.
I've had basically like 10
to 20 people in the stream usually.
And now it's like 24.
I think the other one might have been Shadow Band
anyway, right?
And so maybe this is going to be a lot better.
Also...
I can stay monetized in a certain way where it's like, you know, I have my cash app
I have many website will have the membership program set up
And I have really cool things. Okay. I'm getting
Me see I have a
Beautiful thank you so much
Where's the oddie been I haven't seen that guy around
No, I got I mean he was here last night. He was I mean he's around. I'm I'm I've seen him talking recently
That's good. I'm in a couple
Groups with them and stuff. So he's around. Yeah, God is God is all good. Yo, which Goddy
JT we got the CFF in the in the chat today with Jamie. Hey got Lenore here. Hey, let's up Lenore. Oh my girl. How are you?
You had a cannon drive you wave
Sup cat she waved
You got three cats right here Rudy Lenore and Trix are all they else and they all sleep all over me
It's so funny. They're very sweet cats having a sleep. Oh
Sneezing your shit. Oh, he's sneezing. Oh, are you sneezing?
She's the house I have everything with you. Are you doing good with your with your businesses and and all
I mean, yeah, it's slow season. So the store is pretty slow. Mm-hmm. I
Know I said it's more expensive in Canada because
You know, they have like some people live in the middle of literally nowhere, I know Paige
They can't I don't I like paging at Amazon deliveries. Like no
There's a lot of stuff like that where we are too like oh, we don't deliver to your area
And if we they do deliver to our area, it's very expensive to get it here
Yeah, that's I mean I live in like even like Timu for me
Like Timu is like 90% of the stuff I buy on Timu is again at a local warehouse, right?
And so it gets here really quick the only thing they take a couple weeks and sometimes if it's coming right from China
It's like a brand new item and stuff. And so it's sometimes worth the wait
But also I got some sandals on Timo and they're like some of the nicest and like they're so nice. They're just like such quality
It's like there's such a good stuff. So sometimes they make like there's a big stereotype about oh
They're um, you know everything's so cheap and like I do believe that you could find things that hold option
Most of us from China anyway, if you think about it like most of it is like
There are good manufacturers in China and there are shitty manufacturers in China and
From my experience through like using the manufacturing
There's companies that specify in things so there might be a manufacturer that makes clothing and they're really good at it
There might be a company that makes
Couches and they're really good at it
But then there will be a company that makes couches and they're offering to make you your t-shirt because they have the materials available
And that's where things get shitty. It's these people who have huge factories
Yeah
And also, they're giving care with the factory you choose because there's some factories that will
just take what you send them and then they'll start manufacturing it for themselves.
That's exactly, yeah, you get it, yeah.
Yeah, and so that's hard to like.
Be mad at like you these guys make these things or are they just using the scraps from other shit
They made to make you a half-ass version and that's true with so many products
You have to find so many special cereals and something it's probably probably all like the
Like the parts but didn't they have like mismatch or something like sit like I don't know
What's one of the letters these have some
So alphabet. What was that? They had a these have a serial with letters in it. Oh, yeah, Alphagetti
Alphagetti, I like good Alph, General Mills, I believe, or is Alphagetti post?
Hmm. Yeah, well, I'm not a big, my super serial, what do I like? I like, I like the checks
You know checks like um, I like um, yeah, I like the french toast crunch. I like fruity pebbles
What about the jocular?
We have a special guest I haven't seen in quite a while. Oh, this guy looks different now. Check out this guy
Did you shave your head what's going on?
Yeah.
You look good.
Are you getting booed?
You don't seem very drunk tonight.
Uh, no, I need donations for that.
Oh, you need donations for that?
We're gonna donate for you to get fucked up.
Well, I might be getting a little bit buzzed tonight.
Have you seen D. Hi, Canada driver?
I thought he was British, so maybe not.
You must have missed his clips, because I did have some clips of him.
I'm going to play a Dehigh classic moment from the show if I could find it.
Classic clip of Dehigh and I having a conversation.
I need to turn on one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
But I didn't have some classic high. Hopefully I can find them. I just haven't saved
I got suspended for my job tonight. Oh, no, what were you doing?
I was uh
Move my pants down on in the bathroom. I didn't realize the camera was facing me
Well, you're allowed to have your pants down to the bathroom, and there's a camera on you.
What the hell is that?
It's weird.
I mean, were you walking around like without your pants on or?
Misty.
You can see everything.
I wanted to see that.
Can you give me the video, please?
I don't know.
Can you find it?
Can you elaborate?
I don't know.
Dehigh what happened you had your pants off in the bathroom? I mean that sounds like you're allowed to do that. I don't know
Except for showing it on camera part
Who's whose videotaping in the bathroom that sounds like illegal you should be sweet you should be suing for that like
What are they but your perverts?
Yeah, we're getting a lot of information that don't add up here
There's a funny story with my, with my nephews.
My nephews, like I think in like middle school,
there was this one weird kid,
you know there's that one weird kid that like at the urinal,
like will like just pull down the pants all the way.
I think in South Park did a parody of that with butter.
So you were just like,
but they, they barely take a picture of this kid
at the urinal with his pants all the way down to his face.
It was when he screwed my ass actually.
So when I was in grade one.
Uh-huh.
My first time going into the urinal when I was in grade one. I had never stood at the wall urinal before and
My pants I did pull them down past my bum a bit and
This kid ran out of the bathroom and then my grade one teacher came into the bathroom
And he's like Joshua pull up your pants and come with me and he pulled me out of the bathroom and
he
He gave me shit man
Wow
I remember a story like kind of similar to that like in kindergarten or whatever like I hear like they say restroom
And I would think restroom meant like there would be a bed in there
And we could go like to get sleep during the class and so I'd go can I use the restroom and I go when I saw the toilet
I was like what's this and I came out I was like where's the bed and they're like that's not what restroom is
It didn't happen.
No, I'm sorry, D-9.
You suspended or you got fired?
Alright, I think I'll be able to hear you now.
Okay, did you get suspended or fired, dude?
It sounds gay, yeah.
Did you get suspended or fired?
Do you hear me now?
Super gay well here Canada I talked to this guy for a second. I'll be right back
Canada you just ran away come on come Canada I was I was gonna you talk to him. Hey, look at this guy. I can't hear you, dude
Ooh, they're close
Oh, wow
Okay, okay, I can't hear you my friends
You look good though you look good do you hear me? Okay, here's me
I can't hear you. I don't know. Let me check your microphone my friend
Try that
Oh, there you are. I hear you. I hear you now
Fixed it
miracle
Oh, I just unfixed it
I just unfixed it
fuck
It's almost working.
I hear you now.
Hey, I hear you.
I try to do the Bluetooth to be able to hear you in.
I can hear you. Do you hear me?
Yeah, I know.
Okay, I can hear you.
Yeah.
So you're looking good though.
How are you doing?
Are you okay?
Other than your job thing?
I mean, I'm homeless.
You're homeless?
Are you in Miami?
No, you're gonna have to come to Los Angeles.
I'm in Miami. Where are you? Are you outside? Is that like a building?
Yeah, I'm over in the GTA 6 area.
Grant that Dotto?
Yeah
Are you okay?
No, I'm sleeping on like the beach
Okay
That's what I would do I was like I would just go go to try to get a tent and I put it on a beach and like a sleeping bag
And it's kind of like maybe like a fishing pole or something to learn a fish on the beat. I
Don't know how successful that would be
I'm gonna be sleeping with the sand I mean we got a beach down you wake up with some sand and sand in your crack
Well, I hope you're okay. I hope you're okay, and uh, you know
What are you on YouTube or kick or rumble or what?
I was trying to do rumble, but I wasn't gonna use so I wouldn't get a YouTube
to the story into that
because it was easiest
Yeah, I mean even on YouTube if you're not monetized it is like
You can build a bigger audience and stuff. I know it's gonna be hard on rumble. Like I'm
I'm I'm on rumble sometimes and I'm on kick and twitch. I actually have my my website set up to
What's up actually I would actually I might have a tour of my door real quick can I mean
Okay, so go ahead and give out your cash app dehyde some people might want to support you to give you some beer today
I'm sorry. I can't but
Someone's on the dehyde
Pretty much
I just wasted pretty much the last of my money out of beer, $9 beer.
see you like the yacht life everybody? I'm on a yacht.
I mean the cruise ship. I'm on a cruise ship.
Hey guys, here I come.
I got special delivery.
Thank you. Yeah, by me. Thank you so much. Let's have a cheers, guys. Cheers for having
I'll put it in. I don't know how to I guess you would help me. Yeah, join my kick. My kick is
Psyche Awakens Tarot and then I can join D High's kick. We can network a little bit. I want to help you out.
You know, just make sure I'll post your here's something on my community board to my friend, you know, I put it in private chat. Okay, I'll get it. I'll get it for everybody here.
I mean, not the kick up with the cash up. Yeah, this is the highest cash up if anyone wants to support him. He's having a rough time right now.
It's not fun.
I was screaming with somebody, and it was my chance to do something again, and I fucked it up.
I'm sorry, I'm gonna go to the door.
Oh shit, sorry, oh my gosh, I just slept, I'm so sorry.
I wish you could go look at my kid and see how many followers I got, and I got the sub button unlocked, and everything.
What up, uh, Swiminy Cricut?
Jiminy Cricut? That sounds good.
Entertainment?
Yeah, let's look at your comments.
Okay, here I come.
Whoa!
What the heck?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure that's even worse to do that
All I ate yesterday was it was a oatmeal cookie and that was like really good. Hey
Oh my god
Hey tricks
I'm starving and morbid
Okay guys, I'm sorry. Oh
Yeah, I mean, I do want to play the joey song
Oh my gosh, this is like my holy grail right here
Hot coffee
Hi, so what do you
What do you do today?
I'm going to
Die into a line kick is unbanned. Oh
No
Oh
Remember when I used to hit on you and you get all mad at me
Hi, get the Los Angeles. I have a bed
Queen-sized bed
All right, fly me out
Fly you out
Sounds too expensive, but you'll share the bed with me
Okay, okay, I think I boyfriend. I'm gonna
Bottle never clear. Okay. Yeah a bottle ever clear. Okay, Daniel find your own way over here
Okay, I'll skip the ever clear
No, it's just a customer at the bar, this is the only place that was still selling alcohol
I haven't till 5 a.m. So I need money now, bro. I need money now, bro. Hurry up and donate
Don't you have like 500 subs
I don't have a fridge, I'm broke, I'm homeless.
I think she's talking to me, but you know what?
I'm gonna say a prayer for you.
I'm gonna say a prayer for Dehigh.
Like, can Dehigh, like, I hope you find somebody that will.
I don't need any more prayers.
Please stop with your prayers, people.
I don't know what else to do for you though.
I don't need alcohol and money.
I don't need prayers, I need alcohol and money.
Don't we have to do shots?
I'll do whatever you want.
I'll get whatever shot you want,
whatever drink you want.
He wants to watch dehydrics
No, I'm not monetized anymore and so
The kindness of donations and stuff like that I do have like a new membership gonna go
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it
I'm 36 WB 36, okay?
Some kind of like lady in a bikini that could find you or something like that
That's worth the money, right?
He's cute guys
Come on
Hey, only fans. They're gonna start only fans. Maybe I'll subscribe to that
All right, go ahead subscribe. You'll start only fans
Huh?
You show your butthole?
Yeah.
Okay.
Butthole.
For sure I'll subscribe.
Paid by the drink.
Yes.
Just make sure you, just make sure you wash it real good.
I'm happy too.
Oh yeah.
Oh gosh.
Now I feel like I'm going to, I slept all day literally all day.
It was like, oh, hey Apollo, how are you?
Apollo, get up here.
I want to follow.
Oh, oh my gosh.
Great.
This is my homeless bag.
It's not available.
Don't you want to see my homeless bag?
Yeah, let's see it.
Okay.
Oh, here's all the extra...
Look at all the creams and sugars they gave me.
They usually put it in.
That's why it was not a cream.
Ooh, they've got a nice coffee cream.
All right, let me know if I can hear you inside.
You can have it.
I'm gonna give Trix a cream here.
Trix, can you drink it?
Oh, he loves it here.
Oh.
I feel okay.
I don't think I'm gonna be able to hear you.
Hi guys, you're on YouTube.
Do you like that cream?
Tricks?
Tricks drinking all the cream out of me.
Okay.
Here you go, babe.
Look at that.
Oh, man.
Whoa!
He likes the cream.
You like the cream?
I'll give you another one here.
Where are you at? You're in the bar now?
You're getting cream everywhere. Look at this cat. Look at this cat drinking the cream.
There you go. You got it. You got it, buddy.
Are you an alien are you streaming from the Atlas 3 uh meteor?
I'm uh, streaming on youtube right now.
Streaming on youtube.
I'm on youtube, that's okay.
Why do you-
This is so stupid, I can't hear you.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I don't know who VIX is.
Can you hear me now?
Is that blade?
No it's not blade.
This blade is so loud.
Well, this is are you on a are you an osempic blade?
This is dee hi guys dee hi is the cool guy. You remember he drank all the ever-period set things on fire
Unfortunately just got fired from his job for having his pants down in the bathroom on camera
It is blade oh my gosh, the bakelips knows your true identity
I don't know. Let's see.
What numbers tonight? Look at
these numbers. I haven't had
good numbers like this forever.
I must have been shadow banned
on my other channel and this
one I'm not shadow. Don't know
right? That's worth buying me a
beer, right? I really had. Yeah,
I really encourage you. I wish
I had a you know something to
I mean, I would, but I mean, tell you, I'm telling you, I have a whole chat here that the possibilities for you, my friend.
Oh, big lips, shush.
Okay.
Taking all my straws and for me all the free stuff they gave me this big.
Yeah.
Look at that and this was the one DJ Electric got me this one love that one
Hey
Guys we're having a party tonight come on come up on on uh, yeah the tiger's eye come up on this is the tiger's eyelid come up on
Introduce this to somebody
Dollar sign
Nice. Okay. Well, I don't think I love you more than me, but I really do love you. You're such a cool guy.
You don't have $10?
Not today, my friend, but you know what? When I do, I'm going to shoot you a little something, okay?
You know what?
I'm going to pay it full.
Okay.
I'm paying things forward.
Oh, yeah.
These are nice bracelets.
I like this part of it right here.
This little stone.
There's a little.
Yeah, there.
Right there.
That's all right.
Peace.
Now.
Is there a glory hole in the bar?
Have you ever seen a glory hole? Do you know what that is?
Yeah, we're also pulling the bathroom. Have you ever put your wiener in one? No
I'm saving it for you
You are oh my gosh. I like the sound of that. Yeah, we don't even need a glory hole. We can
Okay
This guy's this guy's a cheap date
You look good. You look like you're like you look like you look like kind of like like powder. Have you heard of powder?
He's an albino albino electric to you or whatever the fuck he does. Yeah, yeah that guy
A warm hole is a warm hole, right?
Bakelips, bakelips.
I think I like bakelips a little bit more than I used to.
Bakelips is not funny.
Sometimes, you know, we don't know, like, how much, like, we were like, you know, similar
people, so we get to know each other a little bit, guys, a little bit of, you know, a little
bit of, you know, a little bit of, you know, a little bit of, you know, a little bit of,
you know, a little bit of, you know, a little bit of, you know, a little bit of, you know,
a little bit of, you know, a little bit of, you know, a little bit of, you know, a little
Let me try buddy
Yours is all the way up
That better
Well, it's best I can do right now. I'll see if my mic
Is absolutely disaster
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
This is a new channel, you know, it's like I haven't been on the channel probably six months
You haven't what oh my gosh
My gosh, you haven't been alive for six months. No, I have I'm not on this channel on this channel
I have not been I have not been for because this is my backup channel
But I changed into cult of psyche and then you get you're back at my discord, right? You join my discord
Yeah
Yeah, you're
You're quite a character D. Hi, like I'm sorry if I like ever offended you or like, you know
Yeah, I'm sorry if I hurt you I never hurt you
Yeah, when you said you can't send me money for beer
Come on bro, you don't have ten dollars for D highs
I like I see your nipples. Oh, don't show them. Don't show them. I don't want to
Oh my gosh, oh there you go guys I got some free foreign for the chat this guy's hot
Well, you know, you need you took off the uh, they're sure yesterday for me was um
What's his name? It was uh
300 glow
So I just showed you my nipple and now you're not gonna donate still
I well, I'm so sorry. I didn't know I didn't know you're gonna show it. That's the problem
I didn't know you're gonna show it guys. We need someone up here to talk with the high, please on the no
We need you to donate for beer
Or alcohol anything give me something to drink. I'm desperate. I
Don't know how desperate you are
You look you know, you look you look you look healthy, you know, you look healthy, so you're eating good, right?
No, I am not eating at all. I'm homeless and I've lost food stamps and I don't have anybody
Why does it trump you lost the food stamps or what are you saying?
Give me twenty dollars. Yeah, whatever
Where people's dilated are you on drugs
You know what, D.I., like, sometimes if there's everything, then it's like, we have everything.
Are you lying? I don't know. The clip that the, um, that the chat is grilling.
I'm gonna do my goddamn kick if you think I'm lying. I'm paying on kick.
Wow.
How did this happen, though? I mean, how did this happen?
Because the dude that was doing cameraman for me,
So, I flipped my camera and I
didn't realize I was pointed up
where I thought I was pointing
out the ground when I was in the
bathroom. So, you had, hold on.
So, you had a camera guy
following you, taping you when
you were peeing or naked in the
bathroom. Why were you naked in
the bathroom? I was hitting
then dream into the bathroom
with me, but I was
such in a rush to go take
Your wiener
So
Okay, did it look good at least how do you look?
Do you have a nice wiener I
Guess it's good enough for the fat bitches
Can you show me private and I can judge for myself? No because you won't even donate to see my nipple
Well
They clips yes, it was I mean, yeah, I mean we don't have to ask this question
Hey, hi, can you hitchhike are you good at hitchhiking you hitchhike to Los Angeles you probably be here in like a week
No, I'm not gonna be able to be an adventure it would be an adventure
Yeah, what if you meant like a really nice like a good looking older man?
You want me to drink with the money? Okay, I'll drink
Is someone making you drink the money hey guys don't make him drink
Panda to the
DHS
Eight nine
Your cash up again to help you out, okay?
I'll say this is for them. This is my payment for the nipple, okay?
Yeah, we're in the fucking chat if it's not there I put it in there for you dude from my chat, so
Hey, I'll show you my nipple now. Okay, so to be fair here you go
I'm like that. I'm all my shit. Hold on. Oh, you get it. I'm so sorry. Now, you're gonna have to pay me to see your nipple. Oh, I have to pay you just to look at me. What the hell? I'm insulted. How dare you? How dare you, sir? God, I'm so hungry. Hey, look at Jamie is fixing the crash out right now. Jamie is fixing the crash out.
Oh my God, I made a read my prize.
Prizes are good if they're nice and warm.
Jamie, Jamie's gonna go to sleep
where she's gonna crash out.
I didn't see Jamie crash out.
I wanna see that.
Uh-oh.
Guys, I think we lost them.
Jamie has learned from ghosts the crash out song. I'm gonna play the crash out song real quick guys. I'll be right back
I'm gonna let you have oh here he is. Yeah, I'm gonna play a song for you. Okay
This everybody going to go find you and
There you gonna catch me I'm falling song
First pitch me a following right now
May I have permission to crash out
Ghost already did he took the whole crowd
That's how you know the haunts a lot
Lights flicker chats in the right
And somewhere goes about to die
Heroes are loud like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks cracking jokes
Keeping the scene clean the crowd starts howling
We have 15 minutes left.
Oh, man.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
That's cool.
They talk slick, why is he still around?
For kindness is rare on this battleground
He saw my fall, still chose to believe
When most just lie and chose to leave
Permission to crash all you do
You loved it, right?
Somebody said, trash AI music.
Ah, ah, ah!
Go tell them to go fuck themselves, okay?
For me.
Go fuck themselves and set my dick for the back.
I'm gonna go with what they made.
That's what I, I learned that from the black people
on YouTube, they say, suck my dick from the back.
Not BG, BG wants to come up here.
Okay, BG, you're welcome up here, okay, fine.
I finished.
Finish it I finished a white claw. I finished my coffee. I don't have another white claw
Eat my food
Great D. Hi. Hey, do you know BG?
BG yeah
Yeah, he wants to say hi to you, so he's gonna come up and say hi
Drop the link D. Hi is what my cash up. You gotta sit in my cash
Me I'll drop your cash up again my friend. Okay. I'll drop your cash up in the chat
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
This is here. This is here.
Okay. So, BG got fired tonight
because he's someone was videotaping him in the bathroom and
this was Wiener. He's kind of cute, huh?
Well, BG is. He's got fired.
You tell the story again with how it happened your friend was videotaping you naked in the bathroom
Okay, hold on
Realized that he had the camera flipped and I thought I had the stream pointed at the ground and then it was pointed upward
Now was on her was this a public restroom no
So what was it a hotel? Are you staying at a hotel?
It was a private restroom it was just me in there, but no you said your buddy was in there
So it was just you and another
He did okay, I'm sorry. That was it was hip you're recording yourself, and you I think they taped your we know
I wasn't recording my goddamn self. I thought I had pointed at the ground
Damn, don't get all mad, man.
Okay, dude, I don't think I know. He's having, he's having a lot of fun.
Donate, BG!
You make it!
It didn't seem like it was someone else's fault that showed your dick, right? But it was really your own fault
No camera guy that have my stream flipped
Okay, there we go again. Okay, so there is the camera guy
There's more than one man in your
When I took the stream to the bathroom, I didn't realize he had flipped the camera
You didn't realize you had another man in the bathroom, and it wasn't a public restroom. It was
Stream from him
And then when I was in the bathroom, I didn't realize that I
How did your work find out that you did this are they watching your stream like how do they know that?
Because people reported the clip
That's crazy
Yeah, it's never worked today in his life. Don't believe that
Yeah, it was it was at the Everclear factory. It sounds
Hey, yeah, so what what made you get out of your fucking basement, man?
Ice Poseidon
Poseidon, okay, so you went to Miami. Ice Poseidon doesn't live in Miami
No, but everybody was here doing a because of JJ's event. No JJ, right?
Hey, do you know, do you know Alexander Mayer's beachy?
Yeah, everyone knows her. Yeah. Well, I think that she is going to
Grandfather me into the IP to wiki.info her site. I think she's gonna pass that on to me
We're in discussions with that right now
I
Turn grandfather. What does that have to do with me though, so like I don't know why you're asking me
No, I'm just saying it. I'll be an I'll be like grandfathered in the IP to
So I'll be running the IP to wiki-dime phone, but I bake lips. I see you
Sit so D highs. What are you? What's your plans out there? You don't have a hotel or anything. We're back
You guys talk
Okay, I'm homeless. I'm homeless and I have blisters on my feet and
You're homeless
food stamps
Last time I talked to you you were on probation. Are you still on the same probation?
What are you talking about oh
You forgot when you put your hands on your baby mama
Now, you're making, you're making
up shit. So, that story is uh
false. The story you told me
that you claimed you went to
jail for. That my baby mama hit
me. So, you went to jail for
hitting her. How would you go
to jail if she hit you? She
hit me and then I didn't want
to press charges and she lied
to the police saying that I
And there was no cops and nobody I mean she's black. I guess you might not be able to
See if someone hit you in the boob
something like that
But you went to jail for that, right?
You went to jail for it
All right, D highs I'm glad you're doing better man, you might be on the run I think D highs on the run
Donate right now. Donates on your alcohol.
Show the blisters on your feet. First of all.
Donate. Donate right now and I'll show the blisters.
Donate. What the hell? Don't work like that. You gotta show the blisters first.
Look, we got a lot of alcohol over here. Do you guys? Don't worry about that.
You think I'm gonna goddamn fucking do shit for you, you know? I know you ain't gonna donate.
You're not on shit, D.I.'s.
How much money were you making on kick?
You probably weren't even making shit.
What do you mean? I got some mutton and everything.
I'm doing great on kick.
Until I got banned.
Is it a permanent ban?
Or what?
Uh, no, it's suspension.
I think that's a good thing.
Fuck you, D.I.'s.
Fuck your food stamps, too.
How come you don't do anything if you're so desperate for buddy? You should be out there providing content. I
Have been that's why I got blisters on my feet
Okay, walking around isn't providing content. I've never seen one clip of you
Not one you can't go look at my channel
No, no one has clipped you I've never seen you on a clip channel or nothing
Just look me up on ip2. I'm probably there right now. Oh, you're not
Yeah, I'm on it. We talked about
No, okay, you're talking about the network, but you're not you on the forum. You haven't provided any clips
Good. I don't want to be well. You're not worth anybody. You're not worth it. Why would anyone donate to your bum?
You don't do anything for worth donating to dude. I'm not showing you my dick you fucking weirdo don't ask that
but yeah actually you know what's funny you did show your dick you admitted you
showed you showed your dick for free to all your viewers because you're you're
fucking you must be gay right you already did that you don't gotta fucking
tell me twice you don't have to tell me three times
Yeah, but you know, it's crazy guys, honestly
You are the type of shrieber. Yeah, is your type of shrieber? That's the most entertaining shit
You could do is just sit there and suffer. I think no one should ever donate to you
But just stay live, you know what I mean people want to see you cry
A lot of men are begging keep begging for dough knows that's your only content
You know, it's it's it's it's
it's it's it's it's it's it's
You want me to do that? No, no, no, leave him alone. Leave him alone
So you're gonna play into his bullshit. No, no, no, no, I don't believe he did that
I don't wait. What do you mean by never come back? Are you gonna like jump off the high rise behind you or?
I'm gonna fucking leave this shit. I've never come back
Oh, there's stream yard
Taking me to my show
Hey, yeah, it's okay. Don't leave the chat. The chat is having fun. We have IP to Lombada
Miss Liz bake lips we have sick is here. You want to say hi to say I'm D. Hi
They say no people to donate for me to get another drink
Well, you know what people like and it's like I
Don't know. I don't know people want to get you drunk because it's like it seems like that's caused problems for you, you know
Shut up stop being cheap. Is it that what got you banned in the first place you'd be in drunk
Isn't that what led you to hitting your baby mama you being drunk?
Maybe the alcohol is the common denominator here, right?
Inhale one of those balloons behind you, grab one of those balloons.
I just noticed you have balloons behind him.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can get high on a helium or is there in the fucking money and I'll show the boost
Damn this guy is fucking
Ruthless, but is he like show me the money is it's German wire. I feel like I'm watching German wire right now
I can't stand with
People come on
Start demanding money. Do you think mr. Beast got to where he was that by just demanding YouTube pays him?
Well, I mean, is Mr. BC even a real human being?
I'm not even sure about that, but yeah, okay.
You know what I mean?
Provide the content first, and money comes next.
Exactly.
If someone was saying to me, you can provide the content,
and I was like, oh, fuck it, what's that supposed to be?
Hold on.
Where's my other drink?
Let me see.
So you hold on Diaz, let's back this up real quick
You said that you went all the way to Florida to link up with streamers and you never even got one clip in
What are you even down there for so were you homeless before you got to fucking Florida or
When you got there, then you got kicked out of your home. They're like, you know what just stay there
How did that go down Diaz?
So what were you homeless before you left to Florida? No
Hey, well your grandma will still take you back man, you're not really homeless
No, my mom got a hip replacement surgery and then her bone got infected and then they found a brain tumor and then
There was like nothing I could do. Here we go. It's a pity party. Poor. She was the transportation. So
Like I had to come here because
The best course of action for you was to get as far away from her as possible. That's how you're helping her
She's bed bound hip replacement can't even walk probably
And you're like, you know what, instead of helping her bring her like she thinks that like there's a fucking dog next to her and shit like that.
Like I was standing next to her and she thought that there was a dog next to her.
This is getting crazier and crazier. I mean, what, what, what, this is like, I don't know if I even believe these stories.
I don't know.
You don't think you believe it?
Her dog is doing what? Hey, Bakelips is in love with BG. I have BG's Q. Yeah, he's Q.
I've never seen big clips, so I can't really comment. Oh, he's gone. Damn. Why'd you kill it? I guess he ran out of
ran out of juice
Oh data, whatever the two
Yeah, well that was that was unfortunate. He didn't even get a dollar the whole time. He was here
He's begging the entire time not one dollar his chat was like I think his chat
Donated something to him so
Okay, so maybe he's getting a drink. Yeah, maybe he's maybe maybe he's like
Success, but let me see it is like four in the morning floor. I can't believe they serve alcohol
There's still people out there drinking at four in the morning. That's crazy. It's not pretty sure they serve alcohol till three
I don't know about four though
Good right now. It's for them. It's 413 in Florida. I believe he's a dumbass. So he's a scammer
He can't even get alcohol and he's like I need money for a drink
Well, hey, babe. Well
Look that guy
Yeah, I mean, but he's I don't know
I just don't know how much of a story to believe but I don't know how he got like, you know
In trouble at work for his own stream like unless they have people like watching his dream at work
Like I don't even have a job. Okay. So then why does he need money if he's been working this whole time?
well
These are the mysteries of the universe, you know
He's just a habitual liar if his family really needed fucking help. He would have stayed. He wouldn't leave
He a lot of these fucking assholes that chase ice Poseidon and try to be a streamer and fucking follow in his fucking
Go try to ride his coat tail basically get a variety off of his dreams
Well, they all have the same story psych. I'm telling you that they're all like some a story very similar to what he just said like
Oh, he's trying to help someone else. He's dedicating his life to help someone else and he's it's all or nothing
And you know what I mean? It's like he's no other option, but to try to make it as a streamer. It's bogus name fucking story
One of them
Can you pull a dick to piss? Oh, yeah, he got banned on kick because his cameraman had it flipped
Oh, so we got banned from kick. That was his job kick
That's not a real job.
Oh, that's what he kept saying as well.
He really gets yourself a kick because he
showed his dick on the camera.
OK, well, that makes more sense.
Dehi, that's not an official.
Well, that story, hold on.
That story still didn't make sense.
Like, he kept saying, remember, I was
real descriptive on the story.
I was like, so you were in this private bathroom
by yourself or with the cameraman?
Right he couldn't get that straight. He's like no the camera man flipped the camera
But I was by myself like what so is there a big-ass window that they're watching you from
This
Then a sack you need one of your you have a rogue mod right that ban on my mean account
Oh, yeah, that guy, that guy's a jerk.
I'm gonna, I'm ban you, I'll make sure, I'll mod you and everything.
No, no, no, I don't need mods, please.
You don't need mods?
Fuck.
I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll ban you, I'll, I'll ban you.
All right, all I ask for is to be in a ban.
Thank you, psych.
I'll come back if D. Heist comes back.
I think maybe he's, like, a technical difficulty.
Hey, hey, thanks BG, thanks for, like, sticking by.
I know you're not, like, you know, don't like me that much, but thanks for, like, at least, like, you know.
Being hey man. That was an interesting segment. Thank you. Okay. You're welcome. I come back soon. Okay. Thank you for being here
Okay, yeah, he gets camera alone to the bathroom. I need to find my other drink
So just give me a minute. I need to put on my music video. It's just one second. I'll find it. I'm gonna find it right now
Here guys enjoy
Hey clips, you don't let your hat you're unhappy come on. Yeah
I was just as lost as you
Don't flinch, I've got the scars to prove it through
A doorway cracked inside my skull
Let the shadowings crawl
Whispering fall
Every thought brought its end
Feet on ground, pulsing riot, marching out of the dream, slow, quiet, not giving up hope
I'll be right back. I'll be back guys. I love you guys. Thank you so much
And let a stranger's body keep me cool
You know the spark, you know the gun
You pull the string, I come undone
You say you love to watch me burn
Baby, pain's the only thing we've learned
Not to be celestial
But the way you left was biblical
So I did something ritual
Cause grief for me is silicone
I might have sent a picture from a movie
I knew you crave the chaos I fit cause love like cars ain't never dead
Not to be divine but I love you
Even when I want to crush you
I could never
I still wanna lose
Not to be celestial
But you made my claim perpetual
So I did something sexual
Just to feel conceptual
I might've sent that photo from a stranger's lair
Just to prove that I still care
You'd fall apart cause you know it's true
Coincidence is the way I do
Not to be divine
But I love you
Even when
What was never spoken
Every scar
A holy mark
Every kiss
Another spark
Not to be divine